Guide to the Roy M. Huffington Oil Company Records, 1977-2006 MS 575
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Indonesia joint venture, Badak, and LNG, 1969-1981
  - Badak LNG plant condensate production (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Badak LNG plant financing (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Badak LNG project highlights (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Badak LNG project management (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Badak LNG project task force in Oakland (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Far East Oil Trading Company - administrative services (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Badak LNG project - amendment to sales contract - Semarang meetings (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Badak LNG project meetings (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Badak project expansion meetings with Pertamina (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Indonesian Joint Venture agreement (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Indonesian Joint Venture correspondence (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Indonesian Joint Venture expansion project (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - LNG expansion project (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Engineering subcommittee (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Huffco Indonesian organization announcements (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Badak Field (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Badak Field Oil and Gas journal article (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Operating agreement (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Operating committee (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Production sharing contract (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Board + shareholder's meetings (Box 9, Folder 13,14)
- Series II: Audiovisual, 1975-2016
  Arrangement
  The material was arranged by personal followed by more professional potraits and audiovisual material.
  - RMH family and friends photos (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
  - RMH 30th anniversary (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Portraits and slides, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Mr.Hicks retirement party (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Building on Success video, 1985-07-04 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Machinery + equipment (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - High press separator, 1975-08-23 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Indonesia "Building the Future Together" photos and brochure (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Plan for Gujura LNG project (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Bontang LNG plant photos (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Color photos (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Indonesia spots(Bontang and Badak) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Badak/Indonesia (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Badak plant photos and the Houston office (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Mr. Roy Huffington, Judy Aemes (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Roy M. Huffington portraits (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Huffington photos and negatives (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Office personnel negatives (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Roy Huffington negative (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Business meeting/official pictures (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Badak Field (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - The Great Hunting Caper (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Official photos (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - LNG photos (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Photos for brochure (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Badak photos (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Meeting with Pertamina, 1978-04 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Huffco photos (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Photo album (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Badak reception photos from album (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - July 4th weekend, Ohio (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Badak photos (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Huffco: aerials Salik (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Badak photos (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Allied chemistry Bontang, 1978-11 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Badak, 1978-04 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Ecuador photos, 1979-10 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Badak arriving on dock, 1977-12-25 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Bontang photos, 1978-11 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Badak Field technicians hands 146 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Huffco Badak Pertamina (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Huffco Indonesia photos (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Huffco Badak LNG Photos (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Badak plant photos (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Huffco Badak air products and chemicals, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Visit to Roy M. Huffington Inc., by his excellency Adam Malik, vice president of Indonesia (Box 10, Folder 48-49)
  - Badak (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - IVEC, Independent Valley Energy Company, photos, "Man On Home" John Brown", 1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - IVEC photos (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Badak photos (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - IVEC, "H" photos (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Huffco buyers terminals, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Badak photos (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Posed office photos, 1976-01 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Badak office photos (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Badak personnel (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Badak Garuda airlines (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Huffco Badak LNG photos (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Huffco LNG photos (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Huffco Badak Field central facilities (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Huffco: East Kalimantan operation photographer, 1977-01-24 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Badak LNG plant photos, 1977-03-15 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Badak photos (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Badak LNG project photo album (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Huffco private event (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Huffco: Badak plant operations photos (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Badak photos (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Huffco fair/ plant projects explanation? (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Huffco negatives (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Dr. Ibnu Sutowo photos (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Huffco plant photos (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Huffco photos and negatives (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Wijarso portrait (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Unidentified negatives (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Mid construction IVEC (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - IVEC brochure (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Bakersfield, plump jack, 1981-07 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Drilling note aerials, 1981-08 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - RMH/ board room/ BLA group Huffco energy- GED ETL (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Petroleum energy Rpt (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Huffco logo corp. Rpt (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Turkish office building (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - W. Abdalla #1, 1980-01 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - IVEC aerial shots, 1982-09 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - IVEC models/aerial of rig (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - W. Abdalla #1 oil well, 1980-01 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - IVEC mid construction (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Gastech glassmount slides, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - IVEC brochure back-up F/H (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Roy Huffington professional slides (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Huffco slides (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Huffco color slides (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Unidentified slides (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Bontang (Box 11, Folder 47,48)
  - Huffco geology of the Badak field East Kalimantan, Indonesia, 1974-06 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Jawa Timur (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Roy M. Huffington geologic map contract area East Kalimantan, 1971-01-15 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Geologic map contract area East Kalimantan map 4 base map (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - East Kalimantan, 1969-05 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Structural trends and oil fields South Sumatra, 1970-06 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Structural trends and selected oil prospects East Kalimantan, 1973-03 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Texas Gulf Coast Division (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Building on Success (Box 12)
  - Huffco film Badak project (Box 12)
  - Huffco Badak LNG project (Box 12)
  - Building On Success part 1 Badak LNG (Box 12)
  - Huffco, 2016-08 (Box 12)
  - IBNU Sutowo tape 1 (Box 12)
  - Tape 2 IBNU Sutowo (Box 12)
  - HM team petpourri flash, 2012-08 (Box 12)
  - The Huffco movie (Box 12)
  - Ascope conference, 1981 (Box 12)
  - Pertamina (Box 12)
  - Huffco Badak LNG film (Box 12)
  - Huffco annual employee meeting tape 1, 1988-09-26 (Box 12)
  - Huffco annual employee meeting tape 2, 1988-09-26 (Box 12)
  - Tirada Kansai tape 2 (Box 12)
  - Ceremony at Mutiara (Box 12)
  - Huffco Book? (Box 12)
  - Tirada-Kansai tape 1 (Box 12)
  - Kuriki tape 1 (Box 12)
  - Djak Zahar tape 2 (Box 12)
  - Kuriki tape 2 (Box 12)
  - Roy M. Huffington Kodak movie film (Box 12)
  - Friday afternoon symposium tape 1 (Box 12)
  - Friday afternoon symposium tape 2 (Box 12)
  - Terry Huffington,unidentified movie film (Box 12)
  - Huffco (Box 12)
  - Firing line debate resolved trade with china should not be interrupted (Box 12)
  - Building On Success part- II (Box 12)
  - Huffco annual employee meeting tape 2 edited master, audio enhanced, 1988-09-26 (Box 12)
  - Building On Success part II Badak LNG expansion project (Box 12)
  - Huffco office and Wijarso office (Box 12)
  - IVEC (Box 12)
  - Dale Anderson productions #106 "Huffco version", 1982-01-18 (Box 12)
  - Huffco annual employee meeting edited master audio enhanced tape 1, 1988-09-26 (Box 12)
- Series III: LNG Projects, 1957-1989
  This series is arranged in alphabetical order by project location.
  - Abu Dahbi (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Abu Dahbi (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Bangladesh III (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Bangladesh II (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Bangladesh I (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Bangladesh IV (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Bangladesh V (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Bangladesh VI, gas development schemes (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Bahrain project (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Blackfeet Indian Reservation project (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Burma (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Union of Burma contract for the economic development and natural gas (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Carmel Energy, Inc. the Dow chemical company- R.W. Krajicek (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Colombia, S.A. (Bogota) (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Chile (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Chile III (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Chile II (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - China (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Custom training for electrical electronic and the instrumentation technician fields (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Data for proposed gasoline plant projects (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Deals for offshore exploration and production, 1957-01-25 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Dual gas gathering systems Inc. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Ecuador (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Egypt (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Evangeline Pipeline System gas pipeline project (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Exploration Management, Inc. (Mike Posey) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Fabricaciones y Servicios, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Fabricaciones y Servicios, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Fabricaciones y Servicios, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Fabricaciones y Servicios, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Freeport Refinery Company (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Gem project (Box 14, Folder 13,14)
  - General speeches - F.J. Spencer Houston Research Institute, INC. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - John Gilbert - Jim Ross T.V., radio and movie rights on Jack London, 1979-04-16 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Guatemala operation (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Guam Oil and Refining Company, INC. Melvin (Bud) H. Gertz (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Guajira LNG project proposal (Box 14)
  - Guidelines for the registration of oil and gas drilling programs (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - H.E Sheikh Abdual Azizbin Khalifa Al-Thani, 1978-05-12 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Hungary (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - India (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - King - Stevenson Gas and Oil Company (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Laclede Gas Pipeline project (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Libya (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Libya (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Conditions Governing Access
    This material is restricted please consult an archivist for detail.
  - Libya (Box 15, Folder 4,5)
  - LNG projects (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Mexican deals (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Mexico (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Gas distribution system - Mexico (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Middle South Refinery project (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Mississippi River Pipeline project (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - The Natural Gas Industry report (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Non oil related deals (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - North Central Gas Company gas pipeline project (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Northern Natural Gas Company gas pipeline project Big Northern project (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Nigeria (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation work program and budget, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Nigeria (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Nigerian OSO project documents, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 19,20)
  - Norway, Oslo, Leif Hoegh and Company (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Odeco Gas Pipeline project (Texas gas) (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Odeco Gas Pipeline project (Texas Eastern) (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Offshore drilling, 1957-01-25 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Old Ocean Fuel Company gas pipeline project (Bluebonnet project) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Old Ocean Pipeline project vs. J.M.H. Ranch (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Oman (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Pakistan (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Petrochemical Plant project (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Peru (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Pine Point area Northwest territories, Canada (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Port Allen Refinery Toro Petroleum Corporation (Louisiana) (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Qatar, Persian gulf (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Socialist republic of Romania (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Romania (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Ruby Gas Development International Systems + Controls Corporation Bangladesh (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Saudia Arabia LNG project seascope group (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Syria (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Saudi Arabia (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Saint Lucia, West Indies (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Shrimp boats (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Southwest oceanic area (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Southeastern Public Service Company gas pipe line project (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Southwest cryogenics, INC. (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Superior Offshore Louisiana gas pipeline project (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Tetra Tech International + Roy M. Huffington, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Trinidad and Huffco transportation agreement and economics of total project (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Trindad and Tobago LNG project development plan (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Trinidad and Tobago LNG project gas purchase contract (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Trinidad and Tobago LNG project highlights of LNG sales contract, 1979-04-16 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Trinidad and Tobago LNG project (Box 16, Folder 27,28,29,30,31,32)
  - Trinidad and Tenneco (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - Various drilling programs broker - client list (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Venezuela (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
- Series IV: Correspondence, 1966-1984
  The folders are in alphabetical order by the subject of the correspondence.
  - The Abercrombie Company (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Acquisition committee file no. 1 (Ron Suttill - V.P. acquisition and Peter B. Elliman- manager (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Acquisition meeting (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Ahmed, S.Sir Tajuddin - geological consultant (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Alaska lands Inc. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Al-Haldari, ASMA London, England U Disco brokers, LTD. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Allied Chemical Company (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Allied Bank of Texas (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - American Arab Chamber of Commerce (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - American Gas Association (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Asia Society (Box 17, Folder 16-17)
  - Arnold Dan C (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Ballenger L. Harley (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Barber oil exploration and RMH Nevada acreage (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - The Bechtel Group (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Boyd and Heiderick - Landscape Architects (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Business review and planning meeting (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - RMH- certificate as an agent to sell securities of his company in California (Box 17, Folder 24)
    This material is restricted please see archivist for details.
  - Cities Service Company (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Circum-Pacific Council for Energy and Mineral Resources Michael Halbouty chairman (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Congratulations and holiday salutations to all company employees (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - DeGolyer and MacNaughton (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Deals (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Expenditures (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Exploration program, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 3-6)
  - Exploration program, 1981-1984 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Forbes write up and notes (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - The Edna Gladney Home (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - "H" correspondence (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Hicks, Charles L. vice-president Indonesia and general manager of Indonesian operations, 1975-04-15 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Huffco and Roy Huffington biographical sketch (Box 18, Folder 12-20)
  - Huffington ocean trawlers (Box 18, Folder 21-22)
  - Interferon Foundation (Box 18, Folder 23-38)
    This material is restricted please consult an archivist.
  - Interferon Foundation (Box 19, Folder 1-11)
  - Inauguration trip (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Investing in domestic oil and gas exploration with Roy M. Huffington (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - "I" correspondence (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - "J" correspondence (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - "K" correspondence (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - L.S.B. Leaky Foundation (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Mallard Exploration, Inc. (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Bruce McIntyre and Company (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Natural petroleum reserve no.4 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Naval petroleum reserve no.4 Alaska interstate company and John J. King (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Oxoco, International (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Progress drilling and marine, INC. (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Provident Energy Company Huffco Arizona, Inc.- refinery project (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - The Quintin Little Company (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Reading file (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Raymond International (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Scott, T. Paul (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Southwestern Bell (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - US Steel corporation (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Webb, Richard (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Weyler, John (Jack) R. Ibolya- Balikpapan (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Zicker, A.J. and Arthur Young (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Series V: Addendum, 1981-2008
  - Correspondence, 1981-2007
    - General Correspondence, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 1981
    - General Correspondence, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence, 1987
    - General Correspondence, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      This material is restricted please see an archivist for further information.
    - General Correspondence, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      These records are restricted please consult an archivist for further information.
    - General correspondence, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - General correspondence, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - General correspondence, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      This material is restricted please see archivist for further information.
    - General correspondence, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - General correspondence, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - General correspondence, 1996-07-1996-12 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - General correspondence, 1996-07-10-1996-12-04 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - General correspondence, 1997-01-1997-06 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - General correspondence, 1997-07-1997-12 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence, 1998-01-1998-06 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence, 1998-07-1998-12 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence, 1999-01-1999-06 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - General correspondence, 1999-07-1999-12 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - General correspondence, 2000-01-2000-06 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - General correspondence, 2000-06-2000-12 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - General correspondence, 2001-01-2001-06 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence, 2001-07-2001-12 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence, 2002-01-2002-06 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence, 2002-07-2002-12 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - General correspondence, 2003-01-2003-07 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - General correspondence, 2003-07-2003-12 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - General correspondence, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - General correspondence, 2005-01-2005-06 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - General correspondence, 2005-07-2005-12 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - General correspondence, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Interferon Foundation, 1980-2003
    This subseries is restricted please see archivist for further information.
    - FY Interferon grants, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Interferon correspondence, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Interferon, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Interferon correspondence, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Interferon correspondence, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - IF correspondence, 1981-2003 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Interferon correspondence, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - IF board meeting, 1982-04-06 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - IF board meeting, 1982-10-28 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - IF correspondence, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - IF board meeting, 1983-03-16 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - IF board meeting, 1983-11-07-1984-11-19 (Box 25, Folder 14-17)
    - IF correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - IF board meeting, 1985-07-11-1986-04-02 (Box 25, Folder 19-20)
    - FY grant #36 Inferferon, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - IF board meeting, 1987-01-26 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - IF financial statements, 1987-1989 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - IF board meeting, 1988-04-06 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Interferon foundation (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - IF financials (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - IF: agreement between Southern Medical and Pharmaceutical Corporation (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - IF foundation- board members (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - IF outgoing correspondence (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - IF incoming correspondence (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - IF foundation bylaws (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - IF pledges (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - IF foundation- Jim Bowman (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - IF- write-up (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - IF articles and news clippings (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Interferon foundation- Jim Bowman (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Enstar/Alaska, 1984-1989 (Box 26)
    - Virginia International Company (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Enstar press clippings (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Alpha project (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Enstar Corporation- annual reports, 1984-1989 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Enstar board of directors (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Enstar Corporation board meetings (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Enstar Corporation (ex Alaska Interstate) (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Enstar Corporation appraisal (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Alaska Interstate Company stock purchase plan (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Alaska Interstate Company (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Enstar Corporation board of directors meeting (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Enstar Corporation proxy fight- newspaper articles (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Enstar Corporation proxy fight- general correspondence (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Awards/Honors, 1945-2008
    - Professional corporate publications (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Professional addresses (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - The BFU award book from the All American Wildcatters Association, 1986-1996 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Salzburg Seminar president's report, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Salzburg Seminar president's report, 1992-1998 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Salzburg Seminar president's report, 1999-2003 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Oil and Gas Journals, 1975-1984 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Pipeline and Gas journal, 1978-06-1979-06 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Five Hundred Leaders of Influence (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - 1000 Leaders of World Influence (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - United States Marine Corps, 1945-02-23 (Box 27)
    - Certificate of appreciation from board of directors of Pertamina to Roy Huffington, 1977-08-01 (Box 27, Folder 11)